
let questions = [
{
    numb: 1,
    question: "What does SIM stands for?",
    answer: "Subscriber Identity Module",
    options: [
      "Standard Identity Machine",
      "Standard Identity Module",
      "Subscriber Identity Module",
      "None of the above"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Expand ISDN",
    answer: "Integrated Services Digital Network ",
    options: [
      "Integrated Services Data Network",
      "Integrated Services Digital Network ",
      "Integrated Services Divide Network",
      "Integrated Survival Digital Network"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "How many types of Emergencies are there in India?",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "3",
      "5",
      "2",
      "1"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who is the author of 'Mother' poetry?",
    answer: "P Lankesh",
    options: [
      "John Milton",
      "TS Eliot",
      "Oscar Wilde",
      "P Lankesh"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "what does ARQ stands for?",
    answer: "Automatic Repeat Request",
    options: [
      "Automatic Repeat Request",
      "Automatic Resolve Request",
      "Automatic Resend Request",
      "None of the above"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is an Entity?",
    answer: "An entity is an object such as a table or form",
    options: [
      "It is processed data with some definite meaning",
      "Real wrold entity with attributes and function",
      "Programming Operating System Interface",
      "An entity is an object such as a table or form"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Author of 'Journey of the Magi' is",
    answer: "TS Eliot",
    options: [
      "William Wordsworth",
      "TS Eliot",
      "AK Ramanujan",
      "Robert Forst"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Expand HDLC",
    answer: "High-Level Data Link Control",
    options: [
      "High-Level Data Link Control",
      "High-Level Data Leakage Control",
      "High-Level Data Language Control",
      "High-Level Data List Control"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Secular Nation means",
    answer: "None of the above",
    options: [
      "To recognize a Particular Caste",
      "To recognize a particular Religion",
      "To recognize all the Religions",
      "None of the above"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is Information?",
    answer: "It is processed data with some definite meaning",
    options: [
      "Real wrold entity with attributes and function",
      "An entity is an object such as a table or form",
      "It is processed data with some definite meaning",
      "It is the actual appearance or layout of Information"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "What does DHCP Stands for?",
    answer: "Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol",
    options: [
      "Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol",
      "Dynamic Host Configure Port",
      "Dynamic Host Component Protocol",
      "Dynamic Host Configuration Performing"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "who is the author of 'On His Blindness' poetry?",
    answer: "John Milton",
    options: [
      "william Shakespeare",
      "Rabindranath Tagore",
      "George Orwell",
      "John Milton"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "When was Indian Constitution Homalogation?",
    answer: "26 November 1949",
    options: [
      "19 August 1949",
      "26 November 1949",
      "26 November 1959",
      "26 january 1946"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Expand RMI",
    answer: "Remote Method Invocation",
    options: [
      "Remote Method Invocation",
      "Remote Method Identification",
      "Remote Method Invitation",
      "None of the above"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "What does POSIX stands for?",
    answer: "Portable Operating System Interface",
    options: [
      "Portable Operating System Interface",
      "Portable Organizing System Interface",
      "Portable Oracle System Interface",
      "Portable Operating System Interchange"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "The Leaky Bucket algorithm was first proposed by",
    answer: "J Turner",
    options: [
      "Andrew S. Tanenbaum",
      "Albert Einstein",
      "J Turner",
      "Alan Turing "
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "How many layers in OSI model?",
    answer: "Seven Layers",
    options: [
      "Five Layers",
      "Nine Layers",
      "Seven Layers",
      "Four Layers"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "How many High Courts in India?",
    answer: "25",
    options: [
      "30",
      "23",
      "25",
      "41"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "what does CRM stands for?",
    answer: "Customer Relationship Management",
    options: [
      "Customer Relationship Management",
      "Customer Resource Management",
      "Customer Response Management",
      "None of the above"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "Expand ACID",
    answer: "Atomicity Consistency Isolation Durability",
    options: [
      "Automatic Consistency Isolation Durability",
      "Allocated Consistency Isolation Durability",
      "Atomicity Consistency Isolation Durability",
      "None of the above"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 21,
    question: "How many catagories in Operator Overloading?",
    answer: "Three",
    options: [
      "Five",
      "Four",
      "Three",
      "Six"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 22,
    question: "What does ERP stands for?",
    answer: "Enterprise Resource Planning",
    options: [
      "Enterprise Resource Presentation",
      "Enterprise Resource Pages",
      "Enterprise Resource Planning",
      "Enterprise Resource Program"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 23,
    question: "Who is the first Election Commissioner of India?",
    answer: "Sukumar Sen",
    options: [
      "Sukumar Sen",
      "V.K Sundaram",
      "T Swaminathan",
      "R.K Trivedi"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 24,
    question: "How many catagories in Guided Media?",
    answer: "Three",
    options: [
      "Three",
      "Two",
      "Five",
      "Four"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 25,
    question: "Expand EAI",
    answer: "Enterprise Application Integration",
    options: [
      "Enterprise Architecture Integration",
      "Enterprise Atomicity Integration",
      "Enterprise Automatic Integration",
      "Enterprise Application Integration"
   ]
  },

];
